ILGWU Boston Joint Board Records 5780/055
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series Company Files, 1947-2000
  - Chenic Fashions, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Cheryl Mfg. Corp., 1977-1988 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Chesterfield Dress Co., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Chow Sportswear, Inc., 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Chrissy Sportswear, Inc., 1986-1990 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Church Street South (1 of 2), 1993-1995 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Church Street South (2 of 2), 1993-1995 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Cindy Baer, Inc., 1983-1986 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - C.J. Sportswear, Inc., 1984-1987 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Classic of Boston (Donna Lee Sportswear Co.), 1976-1986 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Clover Bay, Inc., 1974-1978 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Columbia Tanning Corporation (1 of 2), 1978-1994 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Columbia Tanning Corporation (2 of 2), 1978-1994 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Concord Mfg. (1 of 4), 1969-1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Concord Mfg. (2 of 4), 1969-1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Concord Mfg. (3 of 4), 1969-1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Concord Mfg. (4 of 4), 1969-1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - ConnectiCOSH, 1982-1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Connecticut Peace Action, 1993-1996 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Copley Square Ltd., Inc., 1973-1988 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Cottage Tailor, Inc., 1974-1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Cove Mfg., Inc., 1976-1985 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Cover Corporation of America (VATCO), 1963-1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Cricket Sportswear, Inc., 1983-1997 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Daniels Sportswear, 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Danielson Curtain Co., Inc. (1 of 4), 1980-1992 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Danielson Curtain Co., Inc. (2 of 4), 1980-1992 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Danielson Curtain Co., Inc. (3 of 4), 1980-1992 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Danielson Curtain Co., Inc. (4 of 4), 1980-1992 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Darby Sportswear Company, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - David's Sportswear, 1986-1988 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Debby Mfg. Co., Inc., 1976-1988 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Diane-Marion, Inc. (1 of 2), 1965-1981 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Diane-Marion, Inc. (2 of 2), 1965-1981 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Donna-Lee (1 of 2), 1981-1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Donna-Lee (2 of 2), 1981-1987 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Do San Sportswear, 1976-1987 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Dot Togs, Inc., 1976-1990 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Dubrow and Bravman, Inc. (1 of 2), 1976-1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Dubrow and Bravman, Inc. (2 of 2), 1976-1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - D and W Sportswear, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Eastern Curtain Corp., 1974-1982 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Elaine Fashions, Inc., 1982 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Elbe-Cesco, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Elco Dress (1 of 3), 1976-1990 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Elco Dress (2 of 3), 1976-1990 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Elco Dress (3 of 3), 1976-1990 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Electro Flex Heat, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Ellay's Fashion, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Embroidery Plus, 1993-1996 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Emco Dress Co., 1977 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Erica Apparel, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Fashion A, Inc., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Fashion Affiliates, 1978-1982 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Fashion Apparel, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Fashion B, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Fashion Center Dress Co., 1967-1983 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Fashion Sportswear, Inc., 1976-1983 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Fitz Rainwear, Inc., 1976-1988 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Floral Fashions, Inc., 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Flower Sportswear Co., 1978 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Future Sportswear, Inc., 1982-1984 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Geb and Souhan, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Gemini Corp., 1974-1989 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Gil Rodrigues, Inc., 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Greater Fall River Health Aides & Home Service, Inc., 1982 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Green Mountain Sportswear, Inc., 1985 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Griffin Mfg. Co., Inc. (1 of 2), 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Griffin Mfg. Co., Inc. (2 of 2), 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Hawthorne Sportswear(1 of 3), 1960-1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Hawthorne Sportswear (1 of 3), 1960-1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Hawthorne Sportswear (2 of 3), 1960-1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Hawthorne Sportswear (3 of 3), 1960-1984 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Herman Geist Apparel Corp., 1982-1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Holyoke Dress Company, 1958-1972 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Howard Mfg. Corp., 1973-1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Hoy Mfg. (1 of 2), 1972-1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Hoy Mfg. (2 of 2), 1972-1983 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Ideal Bias Binding Company, 1976-1995 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Imperial Sportswear, Inc., 1976-1982 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Inseme Garment Mfg., 1976-1987 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Kaye Sportswear, 1975-1987 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Kensington Fashions, 1976-1987 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Kim and Jim, Inc., 1976-1987 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Kloth Cutters, 1968-1979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - K and K Clothing, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Kloth Cutters, Inc., 1969 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - K and L Sportswear, Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Kneeland Skirt, Inc., 1976-1998 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Kravif, 1977-1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Kristen-Lee, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Lana Sportswear, Inc., 1984-1994 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Latrique Brassiere Company, 1969-1973 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Lauren Richards, 1984-1990 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Lauren Sportswear, 1970-1985 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Lauren Sportswear, 1970-1985 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - L and D Sportswear Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Lea Carr, 1982-1993 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Leading Sportswear, 1976-1981 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Lexcraft, 1976-1993 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Lexcraft, 1976-1993 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Liberty Dress, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Liela Dress Co. (Waterbury), 1951-1986 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Liela Dress of Bridgeport, Inc. D.B.A. Rose Dress, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Liela Sports Ltd., 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Lillian G. Sportswear, Inc., 1973-1977 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Linjay Mfg. Corp., 1976-1989 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Lisa Ann Sportswear, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Lish Enterprises, Inc., 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - L. and L. Mfg., 1981-1987 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Lorraine Sportswear, Inc., 1973-1977 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Louie's Sportswear, Inc., 1987 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Lowell's Lingerie Co., Inc., 1975-1993 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Lowell's Lingerie Co., Inc., 1975-1993 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Lowenstein, Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Lurie Sportswear, Inc., 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - L. and W. Dress, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Lynda Lee Fashions, Inc., 1982-1987 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Madeira Twin Fashions, Inc., 1994 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Malden Mills Industries, Inc. (Glen St.), 1994-1998 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Malden Mills, Inc. (No. Berwick Division)/Berwick Mills, 1976-1984 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Manly Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1976-1988 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Maplewood Mfg. Co., Inc., 1976-1990 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Margey Mfg. Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Margin Sportswear, 1978-1984 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Maridor Apparel, Inc., 1986 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Marie Diane Fashions, Inc., 1979-1986 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Mario Sportswear, 1977-1985 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Mario Valente, Inc., 1992-1996 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Mario Valente, Inc., 1992-1996 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Mar-Lil Industries, 1979-1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Material Things, 1983-1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Maternities Inc. and Julyn Syndicates, Inc., 1973-1978 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Ma-Zel Sportswear, 1980-1990 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - M.B. Sportswear Inc., 1981-1989 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Meltzer Sportswear, Inc., 1982-1985 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Merit Mfg. Co., 1983 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Metacomet Mfg. Co., Inc., 1973-1995 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - M.G. Kinsler Co., Inc., 1973-1987 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - M.G. Kinsler Co., Inc., 1973-1987 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Mi Li Sportswear Co., Inc., 1977-1985 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - M.I. Phoenix Inc., 1992-1999 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Miss Jody Sportswear, 1977-1991 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Misty Rose, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - M&M Sportswear, 1979-1984 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Modern Dress Co., Inc., 1976-1986 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Modern Embroidery Co., Inc., 1977-1991 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Modern Screen-printing, 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Nancy Dress (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Nancy Howard Sportswear, Inc. & Supreme Coat Co., 1970-1973 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Needlecraft Dress Mfg. Corp., 1976-1980 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Mohawk Mfg., 1980-1984 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Neil Sportswear, 1985-1994 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - New Bedford Mfg. Co., Inc., 1971-1986 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - New England Accessories Co., 1982-1996 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - New England Accessories Co., 1982-1996 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - New England Accessories Co., 1982-1996 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - New England Apparel Manufacturing Association, Inc., 1979-1988 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - New England Apparel Manufacturing Association, Inc., 1979-1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - New England Dress Co., 1953-1986 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - New England Fashions, Inc., 1976-1988 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - New England Purchasing Corp., 1988 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - New England Sportswear Manufacturer's Association, 1982-1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - New Haven Coliseum Authority, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Newton Sportswear Company, Inc., 1970-1987 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Newton Sportswear Company, Inc., 1970-1987 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - N.H.K. Mfg., Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Norman Dress Company, 1953-1989 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Norton Company (Division of Siebe North), 1980-1984 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - N.H.C. Enterprises, Inc., 1987-1990 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - New Bedford Apparel, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - New Bedford Etc., Inc., 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Outerwear, Inc., 1974-1985 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - O.V. Dress Co., 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Ozer Mfg. Co., Inc., 1967-1973 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Pacific Home Fashions, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Pant-Her (Div. of College-Town), 1982 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Park wear Mfg., 1980-1985 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Paroma Draperies, Inc., 1974-1986 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Patriot Packing Corp., 1993-1999 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Paul Modes, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Pawtucket Dress Corp., 1976-1985 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Pawtucket International, Ltd., 1976-1981 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Peerless Sportswear, 1979-1985 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Phillips Sportswear, 1980-1985 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Pine Mfg. Co., 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Pioneer Valley Plastics Company, Inc., 1963-1975 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Pleasant Garment Cutting, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Pleasant Dress Company, 1976-1990 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Point of View, 1983-1987 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Prestige Sportswear, 1977-1985 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Priscilla Dress Mfg. Corp., 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Priscilla Sportswear, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Rainbow Girl Coat Company, Inc. (Barton Tailoring), 1970-1976 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Rakel's Inc., 1963-1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Ramco Mfg., 1983-1988 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - R.C.M. Manufacturing Company, 1978-1982 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Recyclers Consulting Group, Inc., 1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Reliable Sportswear, Inc., 1976-1998 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Rex Coat Co. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Reynolds Mfg. Co., 1976-1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Riveredge Mfg. Corp./Clover Bay, Inc., 1973-1983 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Riveredge Mfg. Corp./Clover Bay, Inc., 1973-1983 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - R&M Freight Forwarders, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Robby Len Industries, Inc., 1977-1985 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Robby Len Industries, Inc., 1977-1985 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Robert Mfg. Co., Inc., 1980-1989 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Robinson Apparel, 1976-1978 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Rochelle Apparel Co., Inc., 1980-1995 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Rochelle Apparel Co., Inc., 1980-1995 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Rodman Sportswear Co., Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Rogor Manufacturing, 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Rondo Knit Sportswear, Inc., 1973-1988 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Rosal, Inc., 1974-1987 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Ross D., Inc., 1979-1983 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - RSF Samples, Inc., 1991-1995 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - RSF Sportswear, Inc., 1994-1999 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Rumida Inc., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Safelite Div. of New England, 1979-1983 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Sameron Sportswear Co., 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Samesta Mfg. Co., 1973-1983 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Samples Ltd., 1980-1991 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Schoolhouse Togs Corp., 1976-1991 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Schoolhouse Togs Corp., 1976-1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Schwartz Sportswear Co., 1976-1982 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - S and E Enterprises, Inc., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Shields Industries, 1976-1989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Shields Industries, 1976-1989 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Shorewood Fashions, Inc., 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Siege's Fashions, Inc., 1978-1986 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Sirotto Sportswear, Inc., 1976-1986 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Skafe Manufacturing Corp., Inc., 1976-1990 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Slendertone (Div. of Elco Dress), 1976-1984 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Sockol's Express, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Southeastern Massachusetts Home Health Aides, Inc., 1980-1986 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Southeastern Massachusetts Home Health Aides, Inc., 1980-1986 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Spectrum Mfg., Inc., 1992-1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - S and P Mfg. Corp., 1972-1988 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - S and P Mfg. Corp., 1972-1988 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Sporting Debs, Inc., 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - The Sporting Tailors, 1976-1990 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Sportswear, Inc., 1982-1987 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Star Fashions, Inc., 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - State Pleating Co., 1977-1997 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - State Pleating Co., 1977-1997 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Stedfast Rubber, 1977-1984 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Stev-el Company, Inc., 1981-1983 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - The Stock Shop, Inc., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Stratton Coat Co., 1958-1973 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Sunbury, Inc., 1973-1988 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Superior Sportswear, Inc., 1974-1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Tammie Garment, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Tammy Sportswear Corp., 1978-1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Tauton Dress Co., 1977-1988 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Tauton Sportswear, 1976-1988 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Thomson Mfg. Co., 1975-1985 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Thomson Mfg. Co., 1975-1985 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Tiffany Sportswear, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Tim Sportswear, 1976-1985 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - T and L Sportswear, Inc., 1984-1987 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Town Curtain and Curtain Mfg. Plus, Inc., 1987 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Trends, Inc., 1973-1994 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Trends, Inc., 1973-1994 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Tristan Mfg. Co., 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Ultimate Garment Co., Inc., 1997-1999 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - University Health Professionals, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Uptown Sportswear, 1981-1985 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - U.S. Slide Fastener Corp., 1977-1993 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Valmont, Inc., 1969-1981 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Valmont, Inc., 1969-1981 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Vanessa Mfg. Co., Inc., 1976-1992 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Vanessa Mfg. Co., Inc., 1976-1992 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Vatco Ind. (S.P. Mfg.), 1982-1990 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Victor Bias Binding Co., Inc., 1977-1997 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Victoria Fashions, 1970-1986 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Victoria Fashions, 1970-1986 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Villa Sportswear, Inc., 1980-1996 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Wardrobe Maker, Inc., 1979-1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Warren of Stafford, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Watertown Undergarment Corp., 1957-1970 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Watertown Undergarment Corp., 1957-1970 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - W.E.B. Sportswear, Inc., 1977-1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Well Made Dress Corp., 1976-1995 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - West Haven Fashions, Inc., 1994 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Whittenton Garment Corp., 1976-1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - William Carter Co., 1970-1976 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - William Schwartz Sportswear Company, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Workers Foundation, Inc. (D.B.A. Worker Assistance Center), 1985-1987 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Workroom for Designers, Inc., 1982-1986 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Z Sportswear Limited, 1985-1988 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Zayre, 1975-1989 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - A and A Mfg. Co., Inc., 1980-2001 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - A and A Mfg. Co., Inc., 1980-2001 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - A and A Mfg. Co., Inc., 1980-2001 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Aberdeen Mfg. Corp., 1972-1994 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Aberdeen Mfg. Corp., 1972-1994 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - A.G. Sportswear, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Anthony Roberts, Inc., 1976-1979 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Avon Trading, 1977-2002 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Avon Trading, 1977-2002 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Baron-Abramson Co., 1979-1994 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Bertrand Mfg. Co., Inc., 1976-1994 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Bertrand Mfg. Co., Inc., 1976-1994 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Beverly Fashions, Inc., 1972-1981 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - B and F Corp. (B and S Corp.), 1966-1973 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - B.J. Fashions, Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Boardwalk (D.B.A. Park Place), 1978-1981 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Bobbie Fashions, Inc., 1965-1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Bobbie Fashions, Inc., 1965-1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Bobby's Casuals, Inc., 1973-1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Bonnie Lou Fashions, Inc., 1959-1984 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Borg Textile, 1968-1975 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Bristol Fashions, Inc., 1974-1977 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Breckenridge, 1979-1984 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Bunny Mfg. Co., 1966-1982 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Calvin Klein Jeanswear, 1991-1999 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Calvin Klein Jeanswear, 1991-1999 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Calvin Klein Sport, Inc., 1982-1994 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Cambridge Coat, 1979-1987 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - The Cambridge Co., Inc., 1976-1984 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Capitol Swimwear, Inc., 1972-1985 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Cardot Mfg., Co., 1978 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Catamount Dyers, 1972-1983 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Catamount Dyers, 1972-1983 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Catamount Dyers, 1972-1983 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Catamount Dyers, 1972-1983 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Cedar Dress Co., 1950-1977 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Cindy Sportswear, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - College-Town, Inc., 1979-1988 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - College-Town, Inc., 1979-1988 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - College-Town, Inc., 1979-1988 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - College-Town, Inc., 1979-1988 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - L. Coracci and Sons, 1952-1978 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Craig Byron Dress Co., Inc., 1977-1986 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Danielson Curtain Co., 1976-1991 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Debwear Dress Co. (Dibner Co.), 1950-1981 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Domenico, 1977-1986 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Emple Knitting Mills, 1977-1989 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Emple Knitting Mills, 1977-1989 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Fall River Clothing Mfg. Co., Inc., 1973-1977 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Family Fashions, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Family Sportswear, Inc., 1979-1986 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - 4 Seasons Sportswear, Inc., 1978-1986 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Futuramik Industries, 1981-1992 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Futuramik Industries, 1981-1992 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Futuramik Industries, 1981-1992 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Futuramik Industries, 1981-1992 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Greylock Mountain Industries, Inc., 1976-1983 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Greylock Mountain Industries, Inc., 1976-1983 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Hamlet Textiles, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Golia Dress Mfg. Co., 1967-1991 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Granite Dress Co., 1973-1978 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Hartford Faience Co., 1985-1990 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Hartford Faience Co., 1985-1990 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Holyoke Dress Company, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Honeybee Sportswear, Inc., 1977 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Housatonic Products, Inc., 1975 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Hunter Inflated Products, Inc., 1976-1985 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Hunter Outdoor Products, 1967-1974 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Hyannis Sportswear, 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - James Co., Inc., 1973-1976 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Jaton Corporation, 1976-1988 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Kala Mfg. Corp., Inc. (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Kay Windsor, Inc., 1973-1991 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Kay Windsor, Inc., 1973-1991 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Kay Windsor, Inc., 1973-1991 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - K and G Belt Co., 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - K and G Mf. Co., 1976 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - K-Togs, Inc., 1973-1979 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Lady Carlton Coat Co., Inc., 1976-1986 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Lebanon Knitting Mill, 1969-1976 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Lebanon Knitting Mill, 1969-1976 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Lebanon Knitting Mill, 1969-1976 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Leslie Fay, 1982-1993 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Leslie Fay, 1982-1993 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Lindy's Sportswear, Inc., 1976-1997 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Louis Mfg., Inc., 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Mafro Products Corp. Inc. / New England Accessories (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Mafro Products Corp. Inc. / New England Accessories (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Mafro Products Corp. Inc. / New England Accessories (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Martine Sportswear, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - M.H. Fine, 1976-1998 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - M and G Sportswear, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Michael's, Inc., 1979-1985 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Mohawk East, 1979-1985 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Mohawk East, 1979-1985 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Muriel Frocks, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - N.B.C. Garment Mfg. Co., 1977-1982 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - New England Mackintosh, 1969-1990 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - New England Mackintosh, 1969-1990 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Newport Mfg., Inc., 1978-1984 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Novelty Textile Mills, Inc., 1953-1993 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Novelty Textile Mills, Inc., 1953-1993 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Paramount Sportswear, Inc., 1973-1976 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Pen Jay, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - P and L Sportswear, 1976-1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Push N' Shove Ltd., Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Putnam Mfg. Co., 1959-1975 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Puritan Fashions Corp., 1973-1988 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Randy Sportswear, Inc., 1976-1981 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Rex Coat and Suit, Inc., 1974-1981 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Rimoldi Sportswear, Inc., 1972-1988 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - River Bay Coat Co., 1979-1988 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - River Bay Coat Co., 1979-1988 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - R and K, 1966-1976 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Robby Len, 1949-1998 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Robby Len, 1949-1998 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Robby Len, 1949-1998 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Robby Len, 1949-1998 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Rocliff Corp., 1974-1988 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Royal Robes of Bristol, 1977-1984 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Royal Robes, Inc., 1975-1986 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Sandy Apparel Corp., 1975-1979 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Sawyer St. Mfg., 1985-1989 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Servall Mfg. Corp., 1973-1982 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Servus Rubber Co., 1969-1978 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - S. Greenberg Co., 1976-1985 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - S and J Mfg., 1980-1982 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - South Bay Coat Co., Inc., 1979-1987 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Stafford Garment Mfg. Inc., 1976-1980 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Strick Dress Co., Inc., 1970-1973 (Box 29, Folder 6)